cleancredit.org.au 2016-05-18

# Clean Credit | Privacy Policy | Clean Credit Australia

Clean Credit Pty Ltd takes your privacy very seriously and has a strong privacy policy in place to manage and protect any personal information we may receive during the course of conducting our business.

Our systems and procedures and been developed with you in mind. It is important to us that you understand the great care which we intend to treat your personal information. The definition of personal information is defined as any information about an identifiable person. Please note that Clean Credit Pty Ltd does reserve the right to adjust or change this policy at anytime without notice. 

Each time our website is visited, a record is kept and this information is used for statistical purposes. 

The type of information gathered from visits to our website include but are not limited to: 

  * Pages accessed on the website
  * Documents downloaded
  * The type of browser used to access the website
  * Information entered into the website.  This would include names, email address, phone numbers etc.

#### Access to Information Collected

Clean Credit Pty ltd may make contact or market to individuals with regard to products and services.  In the event of an external investigation by a government body or law enforcement agency, rights may be exercised that will make available records of our Internet Service Provider and in turn records of our website activity. Unless legally required, Clean Credit will never make available any personal information to an unauthorized third party without written or verbal consent being obtained. 

Clean Credit reserves the right to promote its products and services via electronic and hard copy medium.  The general public may at anytime opt-out of marketing promotion by either selecting the “manage your subscription” at the bottom of the email or making contact with Clean Credit Pty Ltd in a direct capacity and requesting the associated personal information is removed from our record. 

#### Personal Information Collected

All personal information received by Clean Credit Pty Ltd is to be treated as strictly confidential and is protected by the Privacy Act of 1988. Clean Credit Pty Ltd reserves the right to retain information provided including but not limited to financial data, names and personal contacts details etc. If a postal or email address is freely supplied to us, Clean Credit Pty Ltd reserves the right to promote the products and services of the company. If Clean Credit Pty Ltd receives contact phone numbers freely, Clean Credit Pty Ltd reserves the right to utilise these numbers in order to promote the companies products and services. This activity may be stopped at anytime by contacting Clean Credit Pty Ltd either in writing or in a direct capacity and requesting the details no longer be used for this function. 

Clean Credit Pty Ltd may if required by law release information to any government body or law enforcement agency or under direct request by the courts. 

Clean Credit Pty Ltd will never make contact numbers, addresses or financial information available to any party that is not associated with Clean Credit Pty Ltd, without prior consent. Clean Credit Pty Ltd may make personal information available to a third party for the purposes of marketing products and services that may be relevant.  This activity may be stopped at anytime by contacting Clean Credit Pty Ltd either in writing or in a direct capacity and requesting the details no longer be used for this function. 

No information should be submitted to Clean Credit Pty Ltd by children 16 years of age or under without their parent’s or guardian’s consent. We do not monitor the age of our user audience. 

We are informed by our internet service provider that no cookies are to be utilised on our website other than those associated with the search engine. 

For more information about our privacy policy and practices, write to us at: 

P.O. Box 496 Haberfield NSW 2045
